ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
=Blooms for Her=
=Episode 21=
No!
Jian!
ظآزLies born in the mire of schemesظآز
Don't do this!
Jian!
Murong Jinghe, listen to me!
Take her away.
Take care of her.
No!
Open the gate!
It's okay, Shiqi.
Forget me, go on ahead!
Jian!
Leave!
No!
ظآزIf all our past were lostظآز
Shiqi!
Keep going! Don't look back!
ظآزI'll let youظآز
Jian,
open the gate!
ظآزEnd itظآز
We promised to leave together!
ظآزA winter of lies falling once againظآز
ظآزLet meظآز
Jian!
ظآزFor the tenderness in your eyesظآز
You promised me!
We promised we'd survive together!
You can't break your word!
Open it!
Jian!
Leave!
Let's go.
Or he'll die for nothing.
Hurry, go!
ظآزCause and effect intertwine,
a doomed fate unfoldsظآز
ظآزWriting our farewellظآز
ظآزThe red candle flickers on the tableظآز
ظآزAnd I fall againظآز
ظآزGently holding your faceظآز
ظآزJust a little closerظآز
ظآزI'd gladly drink poison
to quench my thirst for youظآز
ظآزA foolish dream
that can never come trueظآز
ظآزLet me indulgeظآز
ظآزIn one final longingظآز
ظآزFor the tenderness in your eyesظآز
ظآزOne last kiss,
lingering and bittersweetظآز
ظآزMay we never meet again
in another lifeظآز
ظآزYour blade burns with my heart's bloodظآز
ظآزPiercing through everything
in my dreamظآز
ظآزYou are the obsession I can't let goظآز
ظآزAn unsolvable fate in this lifeظآز
Jian.
(Once you're avenged,)
(let's leave the Shadow Bureau)
(and live in seclusion.)
(What do you say?)
(Sounds great. Deal then.)
ظآزBurn awayظآز
ظآزThat snowstorm buried in my memoriesظآز
(Shiqi...)
ظآزLet meظآز
(Live well.)
(Survive this.)
ظآزOne last kiss,
lingering and bittersweetظآز
ظآزMay we never meet again
in another lifeظآز
The pursuers haven't caught up yet.
Let's take shelter here for now.
This place...
It feels strangely familiar.
This was my home.
I lived here until I was ten.
My parents were still alive back then.
But then
the Shadow Bureau's assassins came.
My father is
the head of the Bureau.
You knew?
I only found out recently myself.
Your mother was
my mother's personal maid in Daliang.
Back then, my mother tried
to escape Father's control.
Your mother helped her flee here.
But in the end...
Go inside!
Mother was captured and taken back.
And your parents died because of it.
After we returned,
the Empress tormented
my mother endlessly.
Father just watched.
In the end, my mother
set fire to her chambers
and was burned to death.
There's no such thing
as father-son love in the palace.
I won him this empire,
but he just stood there
while Murong Xuanlie paralyzed my legs.
He never saw me as his son.
Why should I consider him my father?
This is our revenge.
This is
a toast to Jian.
He held off an army for us.
Even dying, he told us not to look back.
This is
a toast to Pei Du.
(Your Highness,)
(it won't be easy.)
(I can only take you this far.)
(Shiqi.)
(Keep going.)
(Live well, even just for me.)
Jian.
ظآزMoonlight spills like quiet tidesظآز
ظآزA celestial bird
brushes the mountain's edgeظآز
ظآزWings of light drift through the airظآز
ظآزLike blossoms that refuse to fadeظآز
ظآزIt asks no right or wrongظآز
ظآزNor fears the turning of fateظآز
ظآزA trace of spring on the windظآز
ظآزA whisper of a broken heartظآز
ظآزA farewell song unfoldsظآز
ظآزCarrying every sorrow within itظآز
ظآزKarma weaves its endless threadظآز
ظآزAnd I would follow you
without turning backظآز
ظآزLife and death become
nothing sharp or finalظآز
ظآزLove and hate are carried away
on the breezeظآز
ظآزBefore freedom is ever reachedظآز
ظآزOne must first dissolve into tearsظآز
ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
ظآزTwo hearts leaning into one anotherظآز
ظآزPerfectly, impossibly rightظآز